I live in a very old town which is surrounded by beautiful woods.
我住在一个古老小镇上, 被美丽的树林环绕着.
It is a famous beauty spot.
这是一个著名的风景胜地.
On Sundays, hundreds of people come from the city to see our town
每适星期天,有成百的人从城里来观赏我们的小镇,
and to walk through the woods.
并在树林中散步.
Visitors have been asked to keep the woods clean and tidy.
游客已被告知要保持树林的整洁.
Litter baskets have been placed under the trees,
树下都已设置了废物筐,
but people still throw their rubbish everywhere.
但是人们仍到处扔垃圾.
Last Wednesday, I went for a walk in the woods.
上星期三我到树林里去散步.
What I saw made me very sad.
我所见到的一切使我非常难过.
I counted seven old cars and three old refrigerators.
我数了一下,有7辆旧汽车和3个旧冰箱.
The litter baskets were empty
废物筐是空的,
and the ground was covered with pieces of paper, cigarette ends, old tyres,
而满地都是纸片、烟头、旧轮胎,
empty bottles and rusty tins.
空瓶子和生锈的空罐头盒.
Among the rubbish, I found a sign which said,
在垃圾中我发现了一块牌子,上面写着：
Anyone who leaves litter in these woods will be prosecuted!'
“凡在此树林里丢弃垃圾者,将依法处置.”